A Guide to the Papers of the Tucker, Harrison and Smith Families, 1790-1940
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1904 Feb. 20, ALS (Box 34)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to brother-in-law, Francis H. Smith 1904 Feb. 26 & May 4, 2 ALS (Box 34)
- Parish and Schroeder to C. W. Kent 1904 March 18 & July 20, 2 TLS (Box 34)
- John S. Mosby to Francis H. Smith 1904 March 23, ALS (Box 34)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1904 March 25-Dec. 23, 3 ALS (Box 34)
- Parish and Schroeder to C. W. Kent 1904 March 28 & April 11, 2 TLS (Box 34)
- M. S. Peters, Emma Rogers to Professor and Mrs. F. H. Smith 1904 April 13; Nov. 19 & Dec. 27, ALS, 2 ANS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1904 April 25-May 10, 6 ALS (Box 34)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1904 May 7-Aug. 6, 4 ALS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1904 May 10-18, 5 ALS (Box 34)
- A. J. Montagne, M. B. Lockett to C. W. Kent 1904 May 12 & Aug. 2, 2 ALS (Box 34)
- Wilbur F. Tillett to Francis H. Smith concerning appointment as Coles Lecturer at Vanderbuilt University 1904 May 17, ALS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1904 May 21-Aug. 7, 4 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 34)
- Charles E. Wait to Francis H. Smith 1904 July 15, ALS (Box 34)
- Edward T. Sanford to C. W. Kent 1904 July 16, TLS (Box 34)
- E. A. Alderman to C. W. Kent 1904 July 17 & Aug. 4, 2 ALS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1904 Aug. 17-Dec. 7, 6 ALS (Box 34)
- Emma Rogers to F. H. Smith 1904 Aug. 26, ALS (Box 34)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1904 Aug. 8-16, 3 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 35)
- Thomas Nelson Page to C. W. Kent 1904 Sept. 24, ALS (Box 35)
- E. A. Alderman to C. W. Kent 1904 Oct. 11, TLS (Box 35)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor Smith Kent 1904 Oct. 18, ALS (Box 35)
- Henry S. Pritchett to Francis H. Smith 1904 Oct. 25, TLS (Box 35)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1904 Oct. 26, ALS (Box 35)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1904 Dec. 13, TLS (Box 35)
- G. Lanza to Professor F. H. Smith 1904 Dec. 15, ALS (Box 35)
- Gillie Cary to C. W. Kent 1904 Dec. 29, ALS (Box 35)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1904, 6 ALS, 9 TLS (Box 35)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Mrs. Mary S. Smith, (sister) 1905 Jan. 3, ALS (Box 35)
- Correspondence to F. H. Smith 1905 Jan. 3-May, 3 ALS (Box 35)
- W. Gordon McCabe to C. W. Kent 1905 Jan. 21, ALS (Box 35)
- George Tucker Harrison to Professor Francis H. Smith 1905 Jan. 30, ALS (Box 35)
- J. M. Van Vleck to Francis H. Smith 1905 Feb. 13, ALS (Box 35)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1905 Feb. 14-May 21, 6 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 35)
- Helen E. Moses to Charles W. Kent 1905 Feb. 25, ALS (Box 35)
- Dr. C. C. Carrington to C. W. Kent 1905 March 15, ALS (Box 35)
- Henry William Harrison to Mrs. Mary S. H. Smith and others 1905 March 28 & Nov. 1, 2 ALS (Box 35)
- Grace Dodge to C. W. Kent 1905 April 15-29, 3 ALS (Box 35)
- James Duncan Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1905 April 17, ALS (Box 35)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1905 April 24-May 4, 6 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 35)
- Hugh H. Breckenridge to Grace Dodge 1905 April 26, ALS (Box 35)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1905 May 6-12, 4 ALS (Box 35)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor Smith Kent 1905 June 21-30, 2 ALS (Box 35)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. Smith (Kent) 1905 July 7-Aug. 25, 5 ALS (Box 35)
- Thomas H. Carter to Mrs. C. W. Kent 1905 July 14 & Nov. 16, 2 ALS (Box 35)
- E. A. Alderman to Professors F. H. Smith and C. W. Kent 1905 July 17 & 20, 2 TLS (Box 35)
- W. M. Forrest to T. A. Cary 1905 July 22, ALS (Box 35)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1905 July 24, TLS (Box 35)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1905 July 25, ALS (Box 35)
- Francis O. Richy to Francis H. Smith 1905 July 25 & 31, 1 ALS, 1 AL (Box 35)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1905 Aug. 2, TLS (Box 35)
- T. A. Cary to C. W. Kent 1905 Aug. 15, TLS (Box 35)
- Thomas Nelson Page to C. W. Kent 1905 Sept. 23, TLS (Box 35)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1905 Oct. 14, TLS (Box 35)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband F. H. Smith 1905 Dec. 19-21, 4 ALS (Box 35)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1905 Dec. 22-23, 3 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 35)
- Invation to installation of E. A. Alderman as President of University of Virginia 1905, Printed (Box 35)
- Correspondence of Charles Kent concerning Library of Southern Literature 1905-1907, 31 ALS, 48 TLS, 14 TL (Box 35)
- Alex McMillan to Charles W. Kent re: Deed 1905, 1 AL, 10 TLS, 2 Telegrams (Box 35)
- Parish & Schroeder to C. W. Kent 1905, 1 ALS, 6 TLS, 2 TL (Box 35)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1905, 17 ALS, 22 TLS (Box 35)
- henry Van Dyke to C. W. Kent 1906 Jan. 23; Feb. 23 & March 2, 3 TLS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. (Smith) Kent 1906 Feb. 6-Aug. 8, 4 ALS (Box 36)
- James Duncan Smith to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith [1906?] April 10, ALS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1906 April 21-Oct. 20, 8 ALS (Box 36)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1906 April 25, ALS (Box 36)
- Thomas H. Carter to Mrs. C. W. Kent 1906 April 26, TL (Box 36)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1906 April 26 & June 23, ALS (Box 36)
- James P. C. Southall to Francis H. Smith 1906 May 13, TLS (Box 36)
- Helen E. Moses to Miss Gillie Cary 1906 May 29, TLS (Box 36)
- Henry S. Pritchett of the Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1906 June 9, ALS (Box 36)
- Henry S. Pritchett of the Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1906 June 11, TLS (Box 36)
- L. G. Hoxton to F. H. Smith 1906 June 12, ALS (Box 36)
- Henry S. Pritchett of the Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1906 June 20, TLS (Box 36)
- Henry S. Pritchett of the Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching 1906 July 3, TLS (Box 36)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1906 July 9-14, 2 ALS (Box 36)
- M. Hekee to Duncan Smith 1906 July 26, ALS (Box 36)
- Henry William Harrison, M. D. to Mrs. Francis H. Smith 1906 Aug. 6, ALS (Box 36)
- [James Duncan Smith] to sister, Ellie A. (Smith) Kent 1906 Aug. 8, TL (fragment) (Box 36)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1906 Sept. 26; Oct. 15 & Dec. 28, 3 ALS (Box 36)
- James Southall to Francis H. Smith 1906 Oct. 25, ALS (Box 36)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1906, 8 ALS, 14 TLS, 3 Printed letters (Box 36)
- Henry S. Pritchett of the Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1907 Jan. 7, TLS (Box 36)
- James M. Garrett to Professor F. H. Smith 1907 March 4, ALS (Box 36)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1907 March 16, ALS (Box 36)
- James Duncan Smith to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1907 March 31 & Aug. 4, 2 ALS (Box 36)
- Henry S. Pritchett of the Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1907 April 1, TLS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1907 April 2-10, 4 ALS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1907 April 11-18, 4 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 36)
- F. H. Smith to wife, Mary S. Smith 1907 April 12-July 3, 4 ALS (Box 36)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to brother-in-law, Francis H. Smith 1907 April 22, ALS (Box 36)
- T. S. Henderson to Mary Stuart Smith 1907 April 24, ALS (Box 36)
- Philip F. Dupont to C. W. Kent 1907 May 6, ALS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1907 May 15-June 27, 5 ALS (Box 36)
- H. V. Brown to C. W. Kent 1907 May 27, TLS (Box 36)
- Mary S. Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. (Smith) Kent 1907 June 24-Aug. 10, 5 ALS (Box 36)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1907 June 29, ALS (Box 36)
- Rosalie Smith to father 1907 June 29, ALS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1907 July 1-9, 5 ALS (Box 36)
- Thomas Nelson Page to C. W. Kent 1907 July 6, ALS (Box 36)
- Francis Harrison Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1907 July 6-18, 4 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 36)
- Lucian H. Cocke to [?] Cocke 1907 July 13, ALS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1907 July 14-17, 4 ALS (Box 36)
- R. B. Tunstall to Professor C. W. Kent 1907 July 16, TLS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1907 Aug. 6-12, 4 ALS (Box 36)
- John G. Bowman of Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1907 Aug. 10, TLS (Box 36)
- John G. Bowman of Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1907 Aug. 14, ALS (Box 36)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1907 Aug. 14-17, 4 ALS (Box 36)
- John Bowman of Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1907 Aug. 17, TLS (Box 36)
- Carnegie Foundation for Advancement of Teaching to Francis H. Smith 1907 Aug. 19, TL (Box 36)
- J. W. Mallet to Professor F. H. Smith 1907 Sept. 9, ALS (Box 36)
- John S. Mosby to Francis H. Smith 1907 Oct. 5, ALS (Box 36)
- John Fox, Jr. to Charles Kent 1907 Oct. 22, ALS (Box 36)
- Lucy [?] to [?] [ ca. 1907] Dec. 2, ALS (Box 36)
- Henry Cohen to Dr. Charles W. Kent 1907 Dec. 23, ALS (Box 36)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1907, 8 ALS, 5 TLS (Box 36)
- Correspondence of Charles Kent concerning Library of Southern Literature 1907-1908, 40 ALS, 46 TLS (Box 37)
- M. M. Peale to Caroline Harrison [ ca. 1907], ALS (Box 37)
- Rosalie Rives to Mary [?] [ ca. 1907], ALS (Box 37)
- Letters to Francis H. Smith 1907, 14 ALS, 4 TLS (Box 37)
- Eleanor R. (Harrison) Thornton to Mary Stuart Smith 1908 Jan. 18 & Dec. 23, 2 ALS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. (Smith) Kent 1908 Jan. 20, 5 ALS (Box 37)
- Henry William Harrison, M. D. to Mrs. Mary S. N. Smith 1908 Feb. 5, ALS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1908 March 20-May 13, 5 ALS (Box 37)
- Lucy Rush Harrison to her cousin, Mary 1908 April 18 & May 11, ALS, AL (Box 37)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1908 April 21-May 5, 4 ALS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1908 April 30-May 18, 4 ALS (Box 37)
- James Duncan Smith to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1908 May 19 & Aug. 5, 2 ALS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1908 May 21 & Dec. 29, 3 ALS (Box 37)
- Correspondence of Charles Kent 1908 May-Oct., 35 ALS, 45 TLS, 7 APCS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son, Dr. George Tucker Smith 1908 June 4-9, 5 ALS (Box 37)
- Thomas Addis Emmet to Mary Stuart Smith 1908 June 29, ALS (Box 37)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1908 July 21, 2 ALS (Box 37)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to sister, Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1908 July 9, ALS (Box 37)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1908 July 14-29, 4 ALS (Box 37)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1908 Aug. 1 & Dec. 18, 6 ALS (Box 37)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1908 Aug. 3-Dec. 30, 9 ALS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Mrs. C. W. Kent 1908 Sept. 26-Oct. 19, 6 ALS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. (Smith) Kent 1908 Sept. 28, ALS (Box 37)
- Correspondence of Charles W. Kent re: Library of Southern Literature 1908 Oct.-Dec., 3 ALS, 4 TLS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor A. (Smith) Kent 1908 Nov. 12-24, 4 ALS (Box 37)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1908 Dec. 2-29, 4 ALS (Box 37)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1908 Dec. 21-1909 May 10, 4 ALS (Box 37)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1909 Jan. 1-15, 6 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Jan. 1-7, 6 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 Jan. 7-19, 3 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Jan. 8-13, 4 ALS (Box 38)
- J. R. Mott to C. W. Kent 1909 Jan. 9, TLS (Box 38)
- Mrs. Taylor Gwathemay to Mary S. Smith 1909 Jan. 13, ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Jan. 14-18, 4 ALS (Box 38)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1909 Jan. 15-Feb. 5, 7 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Jan. 19-26, 5 ALS (Box 38)
- Robert Burns-Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1909 Jan. 28, ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Jan. 28-Feb. 4, 5 ALS (Box 38)
- Annie F. Johnston to C. W. Kent 1909 Jan. 29, ALS (Box 38)
- James. T. Munfee to Francis H. Smith 1909 Jan. 29, ALS (Box 38)
- Correspondence of Charles W. Kent re: Library of Southern Literature 1909 Jan. -Oct., 10 ALS, 14 TLS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Feb. 6-8, 3 ALS (Box 38)
- N. W. Mabin to Charles W. Kent 1909 Feb. 7, ALS (Box 38)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1909 Feb. 8-19, 6 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Feb. 9-13, 3 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Feb. 15-22, 4 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Feb. 24-June 24, 3 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 May 8-20, 3 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to granddaughter, Eleanor D. Kent 1909 May 12, ALS (Box 38)
- Laura V. Getzendaner to Professor Francis H. Smith [1909 May 23], ALS (Box 38)
- Correspondence to C. W. Kent 1909 May 26 & July 15, 2 ALS (Box 38)
- J. M. Van Vleck to Francis H. Smith 1909 May 28, ALS (Box 38)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 June 4-July 4, 3 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 38)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1909 June 6-17, 4 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 June 7-July 14, 2 ALS (Box 38)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1909 June 18-Oct. 10, 5 ALS (Box 38)
- Ruth M. Stuart to Charles W. Kent 1909 July 8, ALS (Box 38)
- Ruth M. Stuart to Charles W. Kent 1909 Aug. 30, ALS (Box 38)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 Aug. 31-Dec. 6, 5 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 Sept. 5-21, 3 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, F. H. Smith 1909 Oct. 7-15, 2 ALS (Box 38)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1909 Oct. 14-28, 4 ALS (Box 38)
- Henry William Harrison, M.D. to Professor Francis H. Smith 1909 Oct. 15, ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, Francis H. Smith 1909 Oct. 21-Nov. 1, 5 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 Oct. 22 & 27, 2 ALS (Box 38)
- E. A. Alderman to F. H. Smith 1909 Oct. 28, TLS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 Nov. 23-29, 4 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1909 Dec. 1-14, 4 ALS (Box 38)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Mrs. C. W. Kent 1909 Dec. 3, ALS (Box 38)
- Mary E. Rives to Francis H. and Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1909 Dec. 23, 1 APCS (Box 38)
- Jane E. Martin to Eleanor R. Thornton 1909 Dec. 27, ALS (Box 38)
- Francis H. Smith to C. W. Kent 1909 Dec. 29, ALS (Box 38)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1909, 5 ALS, 1 TLS (Box 38)
- George A. Wauchope to C. W. Kent 1910 Jan. 1, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to C. W. Kent 1910 Jan. 4, 2 ALS (Box 39)
- Laura V. Getzendaner to Professor Francis H. Smith [1910 Jan. 5], ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, Francis H. Smith 1910 Jan. 13-19, 5 ALS (Box 39)
- Francis H. Smith to wife, Mary Stuart Smith 1910 Jan. 16, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 Jan. 18-April 30, 5 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 39)
- Mary Hunter (Mrs. Joe Hunter, Jr.) to C. W. Kent 1910 Jan. 19, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to husband, Francis H. Smith 1910 Jan. 20-25, 4 ALS (Box 39)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 Jan. 24-Aug. 22, 5 ALS (Box 39)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1910 Jan.-Oct., 8 ALS (Box 39)
- C. W. Kent to Mrs. John W. Goss 1910 Feb. 8-April 24, 3 ALS (Box 39)
- [?] Beall to grandson, G. [?] Smith, Jr. 1910 Feb. 10, APCS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eliza Fielding Miles (Mrs. L. H. Buckler) 1910 Feb. 25, ALS (Box 39)
- L. G. Staxton to Francis H. Smith 1910 March 21, TLS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to son-in-law, Charles W. Kent 1910 March 29, ALS (Box 39)
- Thomas S. Martin to F. H. Smith 1910 April 7, TLS (Box 39)
- Letters to Professor F. H. Smith 1910 April & Nov. 13, TLS (Box 39)
- Rosalie [?] to Elsie Fielding Miles 1910 April 25, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 May 17 & 29, 2 ALS (Box 39)
- Rosalie Bell to Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 May 30, ALS (Box 39)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1910 May 31, TLS (Box 39)
- Henry T. Kent to Mrs. Charles W. Kent 1910 June 2, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 June 8-July 5, 4 ALS (Box 39)
- Robert [?] to C. W. Kent [1910 July 11], Telegram (Box 39)
- Correspondence of C. W. Kent 1910 July 14-Dec. 19, 6 ALS, 4 TLS (Box 39)
- Francis H. Smith to C. W. Kent 1910 July 27, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 Aug. 3-27, 4 ALS (Box 39)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith 1910 Aug. 10; Sept. 8 & Nov. 4, 3 ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to granddaughter Eleanor D. Kent 1910 Aug. 10, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son 1910 Aug. 10, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to granddaughter Eleanor D. Kent 1910 Aug. 22 & Sept. 17, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to son 1910 Sept. 16, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to granddaughter, Elsie Fielding Miles 1910 Sept. 17-Oct. 27, 2 ALS (Box 39)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 Sept. 24 & Oct. 21, 3 ALS (Box 39)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 Oct. 14-Dec. 30, 3 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 Nov. 12-29, 3 ALS, 1 AL (Box 39)
- John S. Wilson to Francis H. Smith 1910 Nov. 19 & Dec. 8, 2 ALS (Box 39)
- J. W. Mallet to Professor F. H. Smith 1910 Nov. 22, ALS (Box 39)
- J. R. Mott to C. W. Kent 1910 Nov. 30, TLS (Box 39)
- Francis H. Smith to Duncan Smith 1910 Dec. 1, ALS (Box 39)
- John R. Mott to Charles W. Kent 1910 Dec. 10, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1910 Dec. 15-30, 3 ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Jan. 9-28, 3 ALS (Box 39)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to [Richmond Committee Merchants] 1911 Jan. 13-Nov. 20, 5 ALS (Box 39)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1911 Jan. 14, ALS (Box 39)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Feb. 3-28, 5 ALS (Box 39)
- Eleanor R. (Harrison) Thornton to brother, F. H. Smith 1911 Feb. 9, ALS (Box 39)
- Charles E. Wait to C. W. Kent 1911 Feb. 24, ALS (Box 39)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Feb. 28-June 12, 5 ALS (Box 39)
- Moley P. Leawell to Charles W. Kent 1911 Feb., ALS (Box 40)
- Lucy Harrison to cousin, Mary [?] 1911 March 7, ALS (Box 40)
- Gaetano Lanza to Professor F. H. Smith 1911 March 8, ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 March 13-27, 2 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 April 5-29, 4 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to son-in-law, Charles W. Kent 1911 April 18, AL (fragment) (Box 40)
- J. R. Lamar to Charles W. Kent 1911 April 20, ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 May 20, 3 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 May 25-, 3 ALS (Box 40)
- Letters to Charles W. Kent 1991 May-Nov., 5 TLS (Box 40)
- Mrs. Elmer Ashworth to C. W. Kent 1911 June 1 & July 12, 2 ALS (Box 40)
- Eleanor R. (Harrison) Thornton to sister, Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith 1911 June 9, ALS (Box 40)
- E. A. Alderman to Professor F. H. Smith 1911 June 10, ALS (Box 40)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 June 20-Sept. 21, 5 ALS (Box 40)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1911 June 23 & Nov. 15, 2 ALS (Box 40)
- Henry William Harrison, M.D. to Mrs. Mary S. H. Smith 1911 July 4; 23; & Aug. 14, 3 ALS (Box 40)
- J. F. Lanza to Mrs. F. H. Smith 1911 July 5, ALS (Box 40)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1911 Aug. 17, ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Sept. 8 & 22, 1 ALS, 1 AL (Box 40)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to brother-in-law, Francis H. Smith 1911 Sept. 13, ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Sept. 22-29, 4 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Oct. 7 & 17, 2 ALS (Box 40)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Oct. 21-Dec. 14, 5 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Nov. 3-20, 6 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1911 Dec. 9-23, 3 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to grand-daughter, Eleanor Douglas Kent 1911 Dec. 29, ALS (Box 40)
- Henry William Harrison, M. D. to Mrs. Mary S. H. Smith 1912 Jan. 4-Dec. 2, 6 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1912 Jan. 20-25, 2 ALS (Box 40)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Mrs. Mary Stuart Smith [sister] 1912 Jan. 24-Dec. 30, 5 ALS (Box 40)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1912 Feb. 8-April 4, 5 ALS (Box 40)
- John L. Williams to Francis H. Smith 1912 Feb. 17-Nov. 4, 3 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1912 Feb. 20-March 5, 4 ALS (Box 40)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to brother-in-law, Francis H. Smith 1912 March 5 & April 7, 2 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to [daughter, Ellie A. Smith(Mrs. Charles W. Kent)] 1912 March 14, AL (fragment) (Box 40)
- Robert Lewis Harrison to Charles W. Kent 1912 March 15, TLS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1912 April 17-May 19, 3 ALS (Box 40)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1912 May 20 & Nov. 7, 4 ALS (Box 40)
- John Powell to Charles W. Kent 1912 June 4, ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1912 June 7-19, 3 ALS (Box 40)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1912 July 11, TLS (Box 40)
- B. Seller? To Charles W. Kent 1912 July 19, ALS (Box 40)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1912 Sept. 15, TLS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor Smith (Kent) 1912 Oct. 21-28, 4 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1912 Nov. 6 & 8, 2 AL (Box 40)
- Lucian H. Cocke to [mother-in-law, Mary Stuart Harrison] 1912 Nov. 11, TLS (Box 40)
- Clara Van Vleck to Francis H. Smith 1912 Nov. 12, ALS (Box 40)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1912 Nov. 12, TLS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1912 Dec. 6-20, 3 ALS, 1 APCS (Box 40)
- Woodrow Wilson to Charles W. Kent 1912 Dec. 17, TLS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to granddaughter Elise Fielding Miles 1912 Dec. 25, ALS (Box 40)
- Henry William Harrison, M.D. to Mrs. Mary S. H. Smith 1913 Jan. 2, ALS (Box 40)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1913 Jan. 7-May 3, 5 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1913 Jan. 11-13, 3 ALS (Box 40)
- Carrie T. (Mrs. James) Pleasants to Francis H. Smith 1913 Jan. 21-Feb. 27, 2 ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to granddaughter, Eleanor Douglas Kent 1913 Jan. 31, ALS (Box 40)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1913 Feb. 7-March 31, 3 ALS (Box 41)
- George Tucker Harrison to Professor Francis H. Smith 1913 Feb. 8, ALS (Box 41)
- Invitation to Inaugration of Woodrow Wilson as President 1913 March 4, Printed (Box 41)
- John Powell to Charles W. Kent 1913 March 5, ALS (Box 41)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1913 April 4-25, 4 ALS (Box 41)
- Mary Stuart Smith to daughter, Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1913 May 1 & Nov. 7, 2 ALS (Box 41)
- Francis H. Smith to daughter, Mrs. Eleanor (Smith) Kent 1913 May 24-Oct. 15, 4 ALS (Box 41)
- James E. Tucker to Mary [?] 1913 May 26, ALS (Box 41)
- G. L. Petrie to C. W. Kent 1913 Oct. 3, ALS (Box 41)